I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Isn't it so incredible
We're here sharing the same tired space
In your eyes, the stars look like
Thousands of bright stars
I have gazed at four thousands of time
Da da da, da da da
Da da da
You build a world of miracles
Some wanting the precious This dream of shimmering daily moments
Return way to my soul Stop me from drifting in my feet
That solid ground I stand So I sing together
Every light I'm giving all goes back to you
Goes back to you
Terima kasih telah menonton!